Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Architectural Drawings
  - Job No. 1001-1077
    - Detroit House of Correction, Power House, Job No. 1039-D, Detroit, Michigan, 1922
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, and Mechanical, 17 drawings (Map-case 34, Folder 15)
    - Detroit House of Correction, Warehouse, Job No. 1039-E, Detroit, Michigan, 1922
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, 1 drawings (Map-case 34, Folder 16)
    - Detroit House of Correction, Job No. 1039-F, Detroit, Michigan, 1922-1927
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural and Mechanical, 5 drawings (Tube 74)
    - Ford Motor Company, Glass Manufacturing Plant, Job No. 1071, River Rouge, Michigan, 1922-1923
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, Ink-on-linen drawings, 28x63 inches
        - Architectural Drawings, 10/9/1922
          - [Site Plan], untitled (1) (Tube 6)
          - Foundation Plan (2), revised 5/23/1923 (Tube 6)
          - First Floor Plan (3), revised 6/27/1923 (Tube 6)
          - Roof Plan (4), 11/23/1922 (Tube 6)
          - Elevations (5), revised 11/23/1922 (Tube 6)
          - Sections thru' Main Building (6), revised 5/2/1923 (Tube 6)
          - Plans of Storage Bins, Cross-Section thru' Furnace Room and Details (7), revised 5/23/1923; 1 drawings, 1 prints (electrostatic; on mylar) (Tube 6)
          - Details of Conveyor Bin, Rolling Curtain, Railroad Tracks and Exterior (8), revised 5/23/1923 (Tube 6)
          - Details of Storage Bins and Conveyor Pits (9), revised 11/23/1922 (Tube 6)
          - Details of Balcony, Sand Tanks, Toilets, Stairs and Loading Platform (10), revised 8/1/1923 (Tube 6)
          - Details of Roof and Wall Sections (11), revised 11/23/1922 (Tube 6)
          - Plans and Elevations of Sub-Station No. 9 (19-A), undated, revised 11/23/1923; 28-1/4x32-1/4 inches (Tube 6)
          - Sections and Stair Details of Sub-Station No.9 (19-B), undated, revised 2/12/1923; 28-1/2x33-1/4 inches (Tube 6)
          - General Plan of Grinder Foundations (20), 2/5/1923; revised 11/19/1923; 22-1/2x40-3/4 inches (Tube 6)
        - Structural Drawings, undated
          - Roof Plan and Column and Footing Schedules (1-S), revised 11/11/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Sections (2-S), revised 11/23/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Sections (3-S), revised 11/11/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Plans of Balcony, Charging Floor and Toilets (4-S), revised 11/27/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Elevations (5-S), revised 11/11/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Plans and Sections of Concrete Storage Bins (6-S), revised 11/11/1922 (Tube 7)
          - Details of Connections to Concrete Bins (7-S), revised 11/11/1922 (Tube 7)
        - Mechanical Drawings
          - Foundation Plan (1M), 12/22/1922; revised 3/27/1923 (Tube 7)
          - First Floor Plan and Section "AA" (2M), 11/3/1922; revised 3/27/1923 (Tube 7)
          - First Floor Plan and Sections "AA" & "BB" (3M), undated, revised 7/6/1923 (Tube 7)
          - Heating Plan (4M), 12/29/1922; revised 5/2/1923 (Tube 7)
    - Ford Motor Company, Engineering Laboratory, Job Nos. 1077, 1077-K, 1077-L & 1077-S, Dearborn, Michigan, 1922-1926 and 1929-1930
      - Engineering Laboratory Building by Albert Kahn, Architect (1922-1924) Job No. 1077
        - Architectural Construction Drawings, 9/14/1922; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue and orange pencil revisions, 30-1/4x56-3/4 to 30-1/4x59-1/2 inches
          - Plot Plan (1A), revised 6/13/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Foundation Plan and Schedule of Columns and Footings (1), revised 6/13/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Basement Plan (2), revised 6/6/1923 (Tube 8)
          - First Floor and Basement Plans (3), revised 6/13/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Second Floor and Roof Plans (4), revised 4/25/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Details of Monitors and Columns (5), revised 4/25/1923 (Tube 8)
          - East and West Elevations, Sections and Details (6), revised 4/25/1923 (Tube 8)
          - North, South, East and West Elevations (7), revised 6/19/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Details of Front-Center (8), revised 10/6/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Details of End Features (9), undated, revised 5/2/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Details of Pylons and East Elevation (10), revised 4/25/1923 (Tube 8)
          - Details of Toilet and Fan Rooms (11R), 6/24/1924; revised 7/14/1924 (Tube 8)
          - Basement Wall Details (14), 6/19/1923; 30x28 inches (Tube 8)
        - Structural Construction Drawings, Ink-on-linen drawngs with red and blue pencil revisions, 30x56-1/2 to 30x57-1/2 inches
          - First Floor Framing Plan (11-S), undated, revised 7/27/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Details of First Floor Beams (12-S), 5/29/1923; revised 8/16/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Details of Concrete Columns (13-S), undated, revised 6/13/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Second Floor and Roof Framing Plans and Truss Details (14-S), 5/21/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Roof Framing Plan, Cross-Section and Beam Schedule (15-S), undated (Tube 9)
          - Details of Roof Girders (16-S), undated, revised 7/31/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Details of Roof Beams (17-S), 2/19/1923; revised 8/9/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Details of Beams (Tube 9)
          - Foundation and Floor Plans of Printing Press and Paper Storage Rooms (18), 8/2/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Basement Floor Plan, Plans and Details of Office Building and Fan Rooms (19-S), 8/1/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Details of Transformer Rooms (21-S), 12/19/1923; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 19-1/2x36 inches (Tube 9)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings, Black and red ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue pencil revisions, 30-1/4x57-1/2 inches
          - Plans of Basement and Fan Rooms (2M), revised 6/13/1924 (Tube 9)
          - First and Second Floor Plans and Details (3M), 5/16/1923; revised 6/18/1924 (Tube 9)
          - Ventilating Details (4M), 6/27/1923; revised 9/24/1923 (Tube 9)
          - Second Floor, Attic Space and Exhaust Fan Plans (5M), 10/10/1922; revised 7/3/1924 (Tube 9)
          - Basement Electrical Plan (7M), 6/19/1923; revised 3/20/1924 (Tube 9)
          - First Floor, Second Floor and Attic Space Electrical Plans (8M), revised 4/18/1924; 31x56 inches (Tube 9)
          - First and Second Floor Heating and Ventilating Plans (10M), 2/6/1924; revised 7/8/1924; 30-3/4x46 inches (Tube 9)
          - Revised First and Second Floor Lighting Layout in Office Portion of Laboraory (11M), undated, revised 4/18/1924; 25-1/2x49-1/4 inches (Tube 9)
          - Revised First Floor Lighting Layout in Office Portion of Laboratory (100M), undated, revised 2/20/1924; 22x54-1/2 inches (Tube 9)
          - Plan and Longitudinal Elevation (117M), 24-3/4x55 inches (Tube 9)
      - Addition to Power House, Engineering Laboratory Building (1923-1926) Job No. 1077-K
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Architect, 8/22/1923; revised 7/1/1925; Ink-on-linen drawings, 27x37-1/2 inches
          - Plot Plan (1) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Basement Plan (2) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - First Floor Plan (3) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Roof Plan (4) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Elevations (5) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Sections (6) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Section "C" and Details of Monitor, etc. (7) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
        - Structural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architect, 8/28/1923; revised 7/1/1925; Ink-on-linen drawings, 26-3/4x37 inches
          - Foundation Plan and Sections (1-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Boiler Room Framing Plan and Sections (2-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Roof Framing Plan and Details (3-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Details of New Platforms around Boilers (4-S), 1/6/1926; revised 3/13/1926; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 25-x34-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Layout of Walkways over Boilers (5-S), 1/6/1926; revised 3/16/1926; 26x40 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
          - Details of First Floor Hand Rails (6-S), 3/16/1926; 26x45 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 2)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects and Engineers, Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue pencil revisions, 26-1/4x45-1/2 inches
          - First Floor Plan (1-M), 6/16/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Basement Floor Plan and Section "A-A" (2-M), 6/17/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Sections thru' Power House (3-M), 6/16/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Details of Feed Water Heater, Water Softener and Misc. Piping (4-M), 6/17/1925; revised 12/23/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Details of Tunnel Piping Layout and Sump (5-M), 6/17/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Details of Platform for Feed Water Heater and Breeching for Badenhauser Boilers (6-M), 6/19/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Details of Setting for Badenhausen Boiler (7-M), 6/19/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Drainage Plan (8-M), 6/18/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
          - Details of Jackets for Stacks and Breeching (9-M), 4/23/1926; 25-1/2x44-3/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 3)
      - Extension to Engineering Laboratory Building (1925) Job No. 1077-L
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 4/29/1925; revised 9/11/1925; Ink-on-linen drawings, 29x45-1/2 inches
          - Plot Plan (1) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Present Floor Plan (1-A), 7/1/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 28x44 inches (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Present Building Foundation Plan (2), revised 8/7/1925 (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - First Floor Plan (3) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Roof Plan (4) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Elevations and Sections (5) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Door Details (6) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Roof Details (7) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
          - Elevations of Connecting Passage and Details (8) (Map-case 9, Folder 10)
        - Structural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, Ink-on-linen drawings
          - Typical Cross Section and Details (1-S), undated, revised July 1925; 26-1/4x47-1/2 inches (Tube 9)
          - Roof Framing Plan (2-S), 27-1/2x54-1/4 inches (Tube 9)
          - Cross-Section Showing Alternate Design for Roof (3-S), undated, revised 7/3/1925; 27-1/4x56 inches (Tube 9)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, Ink-on-linen drawings with blue pencil revisions
          - First Floor Plan, Section "AA" and Details (2-M), 5/20/1925; revised 10/28/1925; 30x48 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Heating Details, etc. (3-M), 5/20/1925; revised 9/24/1925; 30-1/4x47-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - First Floor Plan (4-M), undated, revised 11/9/1925; 29-1/2x48 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Plan of Ventilating Equipment (6-M), undated, revised 12/19/1925; 29x35-1/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Plan, Sections and Riser Detail of Cleaning Plant (7-M), 12/12/1925; 24-3/4x36-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Proposed Arrangement of Cafeteria (9-M), 12/28/1925; 29-3/4x35-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Part of Mezzanine and First Floor Plans (10-M), undated, revised 3/1/1926; 26-3/4x33-3/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
          - Connection Plan of Cafeteria (101-M), 12/4/1925; 25-1/4x30-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 1)
      - Addition to the Power House, Engineering Laboratory Building (1929-1930) Job No. 1077-S
        - Architectural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 10/14/1929; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue pencil revisions, 27x38 inches
          - Plot Plan and Details (1), revised 12/19/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Foundation Plan and Details (2), revised 3/17/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - First Floor Plan and Details (3), revised 12/12/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Roof Plan and Stack Details (4), revised 3/11/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Sections (5), revised 12/12/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Elevations (6), revised 11/12/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Elevation at Northeast Corner of Building and Details (7), revised 12/12/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Plot Plan and Tunnel Details (8), revised 12/19/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - North Elevation of Power House Showing Arrangement of Floodlights (10), February 1930; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 29-3/4x24-3/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Details of Addition to Present Tunnel (13), 4/28/1930; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 27-3/4x36 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - Plot Plan of Proposed Addition (100), 7/26/1929; 19x28-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - [Plot Plan of] Proposed Addition (100-B), 7/25/1929; 18-3/4x33 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
          - [Plot Plan of] Proposed Addition (100-C), 7/25/1929; 18-1/2x33-1/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 4)
        - Structural Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, 10/14/1929; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue pencil revisions, 26-1/2x38 inches
          - Roof Framing Plan, Sections and Details (1-S), revised 11/21/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
          - Elevations and Sections (2-S), revised 4/7/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
          - Foundation Plan and Sections (3-S), revised 12/19/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
          - Underpinning and Footing Details (4-S), revised 11/21/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
          - Details of Walkways (7-S), 1/28/1930; revised 5/9/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
          - Stack Details (8-S), 3/7/1930; revised 7/8/1930; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 26x37-1/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 5)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects and Engineers, Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil revisions, 30-1/2x42-1/2 inches
          - Details of Tunnel Piping (2-M), 10/14/1929; revised 11/6/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Details of Tunnel Piping (3-M), 10/16/1929; revised 1/10/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Plan of Underground Lines (4-M), 11/12/1929; revised 1/9/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - First Floor Plan of Boiler Room (5-M), 12/9/1929; revised 5/22/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Cross-Section and Elevation of Main Steam Header (6-M), 12/24/1929 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Details of Boiler Feed Heater and Auxiliaries (7-M), 12/18/1929; revised 8/25/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Elevation and Sections of Boiler Setting (8-M), 6/9/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Sections of Oil Storage Tanks (9-M), 2/4/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Plan and Sections of Oil Burner Piping (10-M), 1/18/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Breeching Details (11-M), undated (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Plan and Section of Equalizing Pipe Line between East and West Pond (13-M), 2/26/1930; revised 3/15/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
          - Details of Tunnel Lighting and Power Conduit (1-E), 11/23/1929; revised 11/29/1929; 27x40 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 6)
        - Mechanical Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects and Engineers, Pencil-on-vellum drawings, 29-1/2x41-1/2 inches
          - Details of Rearrangement of Piping in Tunnel #3 (15-M), 3/27/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Transite Boiler (17-M) (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Transite Casing (18-M), 5/1/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Power House Gage Board (19-M), undated (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - [Piping Details], untitled due to paper damage (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
            (undated due to damage)
          - Details of Foundation for Fan (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Instrument Piping (22-M), undated (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Arrangement of Water Softener (119-M), undated; 27x33-3/4 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Plan and Sections of Oil Storage Tanks (121-M), 11/24/1930; 21-3/4x34 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - Details of Oil Ret'n to Tanks, Scheme No. 1 (100-X), 10/29/1930 (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
          - [Details of Oil Ret'n to Tanks], untitled (100-X-M), undated; 29-1/2x35-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 7)
  - Job No. 1149-1295
    - Les Cheneaux Club, Job No. 1149 Les Cheneaux Islands, Lake Huron, 1923
      - Construction Drawings, Mechanical, 2 drawings (Map-case 33, Folder 12)
    - Ford Motor Company, Job No. 1198 Detroit, Michigan, 1924
      - Construction Drawings, Structural, 1 drawings (Map-case 33, Folder 13)
    - Psi Upsilon Fraternity House, University of Michigan, Job No. 1200-A, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1924-1925
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architect
        - Architectural Drawings, undated, revised 2/21/1925; Ink-on-linen drawings with pencil and blue pencil revisions, 25x34 inches, except as noted
          - Plot Plan (1), revised 4/21/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Basement Plan (2), revised 1/5/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - First Floor Plan (3 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Second Floor Plan (4 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Third Floor Plan (5) (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Roof Plan (6) (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - North Elevation (7) (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - South Elevation and Details (8) (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - East and West Elevations (9), revised 1/5/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Sections and Miscellaneous Details (10), revised 1/5/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Interior Details(11), revised 1/5/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Interior Details (12), revised 1/5/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Details for Living Room (14), 2/5/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 20-3/4x35 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Details for Solarium and Lobby (17), 3/19/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 19-1/2x42 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Details for Library on Second Floor (19), 4/4/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 20x26 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Details for Main Stairway (20-A), 4/27/1925; revised 6/24/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 26-1/2x28-1/2 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
          - Details for Main Stairway (20-B), 4/27/1925; Pencil-on-vellum drawing, 21x17 inches (Map-case 10, Folder 8)
        - Structural Drawings, 10/17/1924; revised 2/27/1924; Pencil-on-vellum drawings, 24 x33 inches
          - Basement and Foundation Plan (1-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
          - First Floor Framing Plan (2-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
          - Second Floor Framing Plan (3-S) (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
          - Third Floor Framing Plan (4-S), revised 3/19/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
          - Roof Framing Plan (5-S), revised 3/19/1925 (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
        - Mechanical Drawings, 12/3/1924; revised 4/4/1925; Ink-on-linen drawings, 25x34 inches
          - Basement Plan (1-M) (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
          - First Floor Plan (2-M) (Map-case 10, Folder 9)
    - Brown, David Mausoleum, Job No. 1214, 1924
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, 4 drawings (Map-case 37, Folder 3)
    - The Detroit News, Garage, Job No. 1217, Detroit, Michigan, 1924-1925
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural and Mechanical, 26 drawings (Map-case 45, Folder 3)
    - Ford Motor Company, Railroad Layouts at Thirty-Three Factory Sites, Job No. 1221, 1924
      - Plot Plans Showing Locations of Railroad Tracks at Factory Sites by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architect, pencil-on-vellum drawings, 10-3/4x16 inches
        - Atlanta, Georgia (1), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Buffalo, New York (2), 10/29/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Chicago, Illinois (3), 11/7/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Cambridge, Massachusetts (4), 11/13/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Charlotte, North Carolina (5), undated (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Cincinnati, Ohio (6), 11/3/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Cleveland, Ohio (7), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Columbus, Ohio (8), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Dallas, Texas (9), undated (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Denver, Colorado (10), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Des Moines, Iowa (11), 10/31/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Fargo, North Dakota (12), 10/31/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Houston, Texas (13), 11/6/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Indianapolis, Indiana (14), 11/6/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Jacksonville, Florida (15), undated (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Kansas City, Missouri (16), 11/5/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Kearny, New Jersey (17), 11/3/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Los Angeles, California (18), 12/12/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Louisville, Kentucky (19), 11/5/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Memphis, Tennessee (20), undated (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Milwaukee, Wisconsin (21), 12/13/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Minneapolis, Minnesota (22), 11/5/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - New Orleans, Louisiana (23), 11/4/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma (24), 11/4/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Omaha, Nebraska (25), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (26), 11/10/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (27), 11/1/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Portland, Oregon (28), 11/1/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - St. Louis, Missouri (29), 10/30/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Salt Lake City, Utah (30), 11/6/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - San Francisco, California (31), 10/31/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - Seattle, Washington (32), 10/31/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
        - St. Paul, Minnesota (33), 11/5/1924 (Map-case 31, Folder 5)
    - Henry Ford Boat House, Job No. 1223, Grosse Isle, Michigan, 1924
      - Construction Drawings, Architectural, Structural, and Mechanical, 7 drawings (Map-case 33, Folder 14)
    - The Thomas Henry Simpson Memorial Institute for Medical Research, Job No. 1239, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1925-1926
      - Construction Drawings by Albert Kahn, Inc., Architects, Ink-on-linen drawings, 24x34 inches
        - Architectural Drawings, 4/22/1925; revised 5/26/1925
          - Plot Plan (1) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Foundation Plan (2) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Sub-Basement Plan (3), revised 10/1/1925 (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Basement Plan (4) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - First Floor Plan (5), revised 9/25/1925 (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Second Floor Plan (6) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Third Floor Plan (7) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Fourth Floor Plan (8) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Roof Plan (9) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Elevations (10) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Detail of Center Bays (11) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Scale Details of Exterior (12) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Sections (13) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Details (14) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - West Elevation of Corridors (15) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - East Elevation of Corridors (16) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
          - Interior Details (17) (Map-case 4, Folder 6)
        - Structural Drawings, 4/22/1925; revised 5/14/1925
          - Basement Framing Plan; Column and Footing Schedule (1-S) (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
          - First Floor Framing Plan (2-S) (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
          - Second Floor Framing Plan (3-S) (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
          - Third Floor Framing Plan (4-S) (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
          - Fourth Floor Framing Plan (5-S), revised 6/12/1925 (Map-case 4, Folder 7)
        - Mechanical Drawings, 5/13/1925